I'm going to cut open this little pouch here.
This is my solution.
Pour it into one quart of water.
Now, I'm probably one of the only dark room people that actually, I really like using old cooking implements.
This little whip works really well.
I make sure that all my chemistry is mixed up.
I don't want to see any browns in there.
I want it to be clear.
That's my fair cyanide right there.
It's like bleach, it gets on anything, it's going to stain it.
I kind of like the shirt I'm wearing, I probably shouldn't even be wearing it while I do this.
But, you want to be really careful.
I am wearing gloves, and you want to be sure you're in a well ventilated area. So, the next part I'm going to make is Part B. I'm going to show you how to make that part next.